I'm about to do a product review on the
most badass archery site on the market
the Garmin zero a one eye
[Music]
what's up yen's we got another awesome
shoot you straight product review here
today where I'm gonna give you my take
on the product not the marketing jargon
that people are gonna force-feed ya so
face product is inside this little black
bag right here and it is probably one of
the most exciting products to hit the
market for me anyway in the past few
years it really is technology changing
the game for how we do things in the
field and it comes in the form of the
Garmin 0bo site to check that out this
thing right here is a radical both site
let me tell you and it looks radical
right when you look at it it just looks
different than probably anything you've
ever seen in the past and there's a
reason for that that's because it is
different right this thing right here is
actually a bo site with a rangefinder
built right into the site so let's talk
about mounting first a lot of different
mounting options different mounting
holes for you depending on how light how
far out you like it on your bone and
then adjustment features super
adjustable okay it's actually got the
micro adjust for your windage and then
it's got your elevation adjustment micro
adjust right here on this side so then
what you're gonna see on this thing is
some of these curvature adjustments so
you can see that right there that's
gonna be a curvature adjustment to make
sure that you take all of the camped out
of the windage on the rangefinder right
you want that rangefinder square and
point and true that's what these
curvature adjustments for so you're
going to see a windage one right here
and then you are gonna see an elevation
curvature adjustment right back here on
the back of it this housing right here
this housing is actually the housing for
the rangefinder and also for the
batteries so when you look at this thing
right here on the side you've got just a
couple of little allen head bolts you're
gonna take out that's where your house
your batteries put the lid back on this
thing is completely sealed up and
waterproof inside so you don't have to
worry about water being an issue getting
in there water will not get in there
then you've got the front of the
rangefinder right here and then
got your site window your site window is
actually gonna house a scream okay so
this thing is actually interactive it's
got a digital display screen on here
that is gonna give you information
everything from allowing you to set up
the initial settings of language and all
that stuff to picking different arrow
profiles and then right on top of the
bow site you've got a series of four
buttons so you're gonna have a power
button you're gonna have a left and
right button and then you're gonna have
an OK button once the power is on the
power button also acts as the back
button so if you need to go back to a
previous screen in the menu that's how
you do that and we got this little cable
running down right here this cable that
comes off the side this is what
activates your rangefinder and actually
throws your pin up and project your pin
inside the sight window so if you can
see inside that sight window like that
and you're looking in there you can see
what looks like a lens almost it's a
screen that actually is gonna project an
image on there it's going to project a
pin on there for you
this cable essentially you're gonna run
it right down the front of the riser on
your bow and you're gonna put it right
on your grip you're actually gonna tape
it right to the grip and you're gonna be
able to just one quick bump boom get the
range on the animal projects the pin and
you're off to the races so that's how
simple the zero a one is that's it guys
that's a wrap first and foremost want to
thank everybody for taking the time to
watch these videos I hope everybody
appreciates us trying to give you our
take right we want to shoot you straight
not all the marketing jargon that
everybody else tells you we want to tell
you the good and the bad of all the
products that we're using if you like it
you know the drill head down to the
description we've got links down there
if you like what you see check out our
other videos we also have the website
kefir bros comm you can go visit the
website on the website we've got promo
codes we've got deals we've got rewards
we've got all kinds of stuff happening
over there you can actually purchase a
lot of these products right through the
website so once again thanks everybody
for watching until next time peace out